Guide to the Acquisitions Department registers, etc
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Acquisitions Department registers, etc
1922-1968
Columbia University. Libraries.
117 linear ft. (707 registers)
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library New York, NY. 10027
7885692
History
Scope and Content
707 Acquisitions Department Registers dating from 1922-1968.
Arrangement
Arranged by number
Access Restrictions
This collection has no restrictions.
Transfer from Acquisitions Department.
- Series I: Columbia University Library: Gifts
  - 1922/23- (Box 1)
  - 1927/28. (Box 1)
  - 1928/29- (Box 2)
  - 1932/33. (Box 2)
  - 1933/34- (Box 3)
  - 1935/36 (Box 3)
  - 1936/37- (Box 4)
  - 1939/40. (Box 4)
- Series II: Columbia University Library: Ledger
  - 1928/29. (Box 1)
  - 1929/30. (Box 2)
  - 1930/31. (Box 3)
  - 1931/32. (Box 4)
  - 1932/33. (Box 5)
  - 1933/34- (Box 6)
  - 1934/35. (Box 6)
  - 1935/36. (Box 7)
  - 1936/37. (Box 8)
  - 1937/38. (Box 9)
  - 1938/39. (Box 10)
- Series III: Order Books
  - 17000 - 17999 December 8, 1944 - December 26, 1944 (Box 1)
  - 18000 - 18999 December 22, 1944 - January 5, 1945 (Box 2)
  - 19000 - 19999 January 5, 1945 - January 18, 1945 (Box 3)
  - 20000 - 20999 January 18, 1945 - January 31, 1945 (Box 4)
  - 21000 - 21999 January 31, 1945 - February 13, 1945 (Box 5)
  - 22000 - 22999 February 13, 1945 - February 28, 1945 (Box 6)
  - 23000 - 23999 February 28, 1945 - March 14, 1945 (Box 7)
  - 24000 - 24999 March 14, 1945 - March 29, 1945 (Box 8)
  - 25000 - 25999 March 29, 1945 - April 9, 1945 (Box 9)
  - 26000 - 26999 April 9, 1945 - April 20, 1945 (Box 10)
  - 27000 - 27999 April 20, 1945 - May 10, 1945 (Box 11)
  - 28000 - 28999 May 10, 1945 - May 22, 1945 (Box 12)
  - 29000 - 29999 May 22, 1945 - June 5, 1945 (Box 13)
  - 30000 - 30999 June 5, 1945 - June 18, 1945 (Box 14)
  - 31000 - 31999 June 18, 1945 - June 27, 1945 (Box 15)
  - 32000 - 32999 June 27, 1945 - July 10, 1945 (Box 16)
  - 33000 - 33999 July 10, 1945 - August 3, 1945 (Box 17)
  - 34000 - 34999 August 3, 1945 – August 28, 1945 (Box 18)
  - 35000 - 35999 August 28, 1945 - September 20, 1945 (Box 19)
  - 36000 - 36999 September 20, 1945 - October 9, 1945 (Box 20)
  - 37000 - 37999 October 9, 1945 - October 22, 1945 (Box 21)
  - 38000 - 38999 October 22, 1945 - November 5, 1945 (Box 22)
  - 39000 - 39999 November 5, 1945 - November 21, 1945 (Box 23)
  - 40000 - 40999 November 21, 1945 - December 5, 1945 (Box 24)
  - 42000 - 42630 December 18, 1945 - December 28, 1945 (Box 25)
  - 12001 - 14000 December 3, 1951 - January 10, 1952 (Box 26)
  - 14001 - 16000 January 10 - February 8, 1952 (Box 27)
  - 16001 - 18000 February 2 - March 4, 1952 (Box 28)
  - 26001 - 28000 August 1 - September 16, 1952 (Box 29)
  - 28001 - 30000 September 16 - October 8, 1952 (Box 30)
  - 30001 - 32000 October 8 - October 31, 1952 (Box 31)
  - 32001 - 34000 October 31 - December 3, 1952 (Box 32)
  - 34001 - 36000 December 3, 1952 - January 8, 1953 (Box 33)
  - 36001 - 38000 Jan 8, - February 4, 1953 (Box 34)
  - 38001 - 40000 February 4 - March 2, 1953 (Box 35)
  - 40001 - 42000 March 2 - March 20, 1953 (Box 36)
  - 42001 - 44000 March 20 - April 23, 1953 (Box 37)
  - 44001 - 46000 April 23 - May 20, 1953 (Box 38)
  - 46001 - 48000 May 20 - July 1, 1953 (Box 39)
  - 48001 - 50000 July 1 - 17, 1953 (Box 40)
  - 50001 - 52000 July 20 - August 12, 1953 (Box 41)
  - 52001 - 54000 August 12 - September 28 1953 (Box 42)
  - 54001 - 56000 September 28 - October 20, 1953 (Box 43)
  - 56001 - 58000 October 21 - November 13, 1953 (Box 44)
  - 58001 - 60000 November 13 - December 15, 1953 (Box 45)
  - 1 - 2000 December 23, 1953 - January 14, 1954 (Box 46)
  - 2001 - 4000 January 14. - February 10, 1954 (Box 47)
  - 4001 - 6000 February 10 - Mar 8, 1954 (Box 48)
  - 6001 - 8000 March 8 - April 1, 1954 (Box 49)
  - 8001 - 10000 April 1 - April 27, 1954 (Box 50)
  - 10001 - 12000 April 27 - May 19, 1954 (Box 51)
  - 12001 - 14000 May 19 - June 17, 1954 (Box 52)
  - 14001 - 16000 July 1 - July 16, 1954 (Box 53)
  - 16001 - 18000 July 16 - August 8, 1954 (Box 54)
  - 18001 - 20000 August 11 - September 14, 1954 (Box 55)
  - 20001E - 22000E: September 14 - September 30, 1954 (Box 56)
  - 22001E - 24000E: September 30 - October 27, 1954 (Box 57)
  - 24001E - 26000E: October 27, 1954 - April 1, 1955 (Box 58)
  - 26001E - 28000E: November 19, 1954 - January 10, 1955 (Box 59)
  - 28001E - 30000E: January 10 - February 16, 1955 (Box 60)
  - 30001E - 32000E: February 16 - April 11, 1955 (Box 61)
  - 32001E - 34000E: April 12 - May 9, 1955 (Box 62)
  - 34001E - 36000E: May 9 - June 8, 1955 (Box 63)
  - 36001E - 38000E: June 8, 1955 - May 10, 1957 (Box 64)
  - 49501E - 51000E: June 17 - July 25, 1955 (Box 65)
  - 51001E - 53000E: August 1 - September 15, 1955 (Box 66)
  - 53001E - 55000E: August 31 - October 10, 1955 (Box 67)
  - 55001E - 57000E: October 10 - November 17, 1955 (Box 68)
  - 57001E - 59000E: November 17, 1955 - December 20, 1955 (Box 69)
  - 59001E - 60000E: December 20, 1955 - January 16, 1956 (Box 70)
  - 1F - 2000F: January 16, 1956 - February 17, 1956 (Box 71)
  - 2001F - 4000F: February 17, 1956 - March 22, 1956 (Box 72)
  - 4001F - 6000F: March 22, 1956 - April 24, 1956 (Box 73)
  - 6001F - 8000F: March 4, 1956 - May 22, 1956 (Box 74)
  - 8001F - 10000F: May 22, 1956 - July 10, 1956 (Box 75)
  - 10001F - 12000F: July 10, 1956 - August 24, 1956 (Box 76)
  - 12001F - 14000F: August 24, 1956 - October 5, 1956 (Box 77)
  - 14001F - 16000F: October 5, 1956 - October 30, 1956 (Box 78)
  - 16001F - 18000F: October 30, 1956 - November 29, 1956 (Box 79)
  - 18001F - 20000F: November 29, 1956 - January 7, 1957 (Box 80)
  - 20001F - 22000F: January 7, 1957 - February 7, 1957 (Box 81)
  - 22001F - 24000F: February 7, 1957 - March 8, 1957 (Box 82)
  - 24001F - 26000F: March 8, 1957 - April 11, 1957 (Box 83)
  - 26001F - 28000F: April 11, 1957 - May 17, 1957 (Box 84)
  - 38001E - 40000E: May 10, 1957 - January 29, 1959 (Box 85)
  - 28001F - 30000F: May 17, 1957 - July 1, 1957 (Box 86)
  - 30001F - 32000F: July 1, 1957 - July 26, 1957 (Box 87)
  - 32001F - 34000F: July 26, 1957 - August 30, 1957 (Box 88)
  - 34001F - 36000F: August 30, 1957 - October 11, 1957 (Box 89)
  - 36001F - 38000F: October 11, 1957 - November 7, 1957 (Box 90)
  - 38001F - 40000F: November 7, 1957 - December 19. 1957 (Box 91)
  - 40001F - 42000F: December 19, 1957 - January 27, 1958 (Box 92)
  - 42001F - 44000F: January 27, 1958 - February 20, 1958 (Box 93)
  - 44001F - 46000F: February 20, 1958 - March 25, 1958 (Box 94)
  - 46001F - 48000F: March 25, 1958 - May 6, 1958 (Box 95)
  - 48001F - 50000F: May 6, 1958 - July 1, 1958 (Box 96)
  - 50001F - 52000F: July 1, 1958 - July 31, 1958 (Box 97)
  - 52001F - 54000F: July 31, 1958 - September 16, 1958 (Box 98)
  - 54001F - 56000F: September 16, 1958 - October 14, 1958 (Box 99)
  - 56001F - 58000F: October 14, 1958 - November 11, 1958 (Box 100)
  - 58001F - 59999F: November 11, 1958 - December 17, 1958 (Box 101)
  - 1G - 2000G: December 17, 1958 - January 26, 1959 (Box 102)
  - 2001G - 4000G: January 26, 1959 - February 19, 1959 (Box 103)
  - 40001E - 42000E: February 2, 1959 - September 14, 1960 (Box 104)
  - 4001G - 6000G: February 19, 1959 - March 20, 1959 (Box 105)
  - 6001G - 8000G: March 20, 1959 - April 29. 1959 (Box 106)
  - 8001G - 10000G: April 29, 1959 - June. 5, 1959 (Box 107)
  - 10000G - 12000G: June 5, 1959 - July 15, 1959 (Box 108)
  - 12001G - 14000G: July 15, 1959 - August 19, 1959 (Box 109)
  - 14001G - 16000G: August 19, 1959 - October 5, 1959 (Box 110)
  - 16001G - 18000G: October 5, 1959 - October 27, 1959 (Box 111)
  - 18000G - 20000G: October 27, 1959 - December 3, 1959 (Box 112)
  - 20001G - 22000G: December 4. 1959 - January 5, 1960 (Box 113)
  - 22001G - 23000G: January 5, 1960 - January 18, 1960 (Box 114)
  - 23001G - 24000G: January 18, 1960 - February 1, 1960 (Box 115)
  - 24001G - 26000G: February 1, 1960 - March 1, 1960 (Box 116)
  - 26001G - 28000G: March 1, 1960 - March 1, 1960 (Box 117)
  - 28001G - 30000G: April 1, 1960 - May 17, 1960 (Box 118)
  - 30001G - 32000G: May 17, 1960 - July 1, 1960 (Box 119)
  - 32001G - 34000G: July 1, 1960 - July 26, 1960 (Box 120)
  - 34001G - 36000G: July 26, 1960 - August 17. 1960 (Box 121)
  - 36001G - 38000G: August 17, 1960 - September 26, 1960 (Box 122)
  - 38001G - 40000G: Sept, 26. 1960- October 24, 1960 (Box 123)
  - 40001G - 42000G: October 24, 1960 - November 23, 1960 (Box 124)
  - 42001G - 44000G: November 23, 1960 - January 4, 1961 (Box 125)
  - 44001G - 46000G: January 4, 1961 - February 6, 1961 (Box 126)
  - 46001G - 48000G: February 6, 1961 - March 9, 1961 (Box 127)
  - 48001G - 50000G: March 9, 1961 - April 12, 1961 (Box 128)
  - 50001G - 52000G: April 12, 1961 - May 16, 1961 (Box 129)
  - 52001G - 54000G: May 16, 1961 - June 6, 1961 (Box 130)
  - 54001G - 56000G: June 6, 1961 - July 17, 1961 (Box 131)
  - 56001G - 58000G: July 17, 1961 - August 24, 1961 (Box 132)
  - 58001G - 59999G: August 24, 1961 - September 18, 1961 (Box 133)
  - 00001H - 02000H: September 18, 1961 - October 13, 1961 (Box 134)
  - 02001H - 04000H: October 13, 1961 - November 2, 1961 (Box 135)
  - 04001H - 06000H: November 2, 1961 - December 4, 1961 (Box 136)
  - 06001H - 08000H: December 4, 1961 - January 10, 1962 (Box 137)
  - 08001H - 10000H: January 10, 1962 - February 6, 1962 (Box 138)
  - 10001H - 12000H: February 6, 1962 - March 1, 1962 (Box 139)
  - 12001H - 14000H: March 1, 1962 - March 27, 1962 (Box 140)
  - 14001H - 16000H: March 27. 1962 - April 17, 1962 (Box 141)
  - 16001H - 18000H: April 17. 1962 - May 9, 1962 (Box 142)
  - 18001H - 20000H: May 9, 1962 - May 31, 1962 (Box 143)
  - 20001H - 22000H: May 31, 1962 - June 27, 1962 (Box 144)
  - 22001H - 24000H: June 27, 1962 - July 25, 1962 (Box 145)
  - 24001H - 26000H: July 25, 1962 - August 14, 1962 (Box 146)
  - 26001H - 28000H: August 14, 1962 - September 6, 1962 (Box 147)
  - 28001H - 30000H: September 9, 1962 - October 8, 1962 (Box 148)
  - 30001H - 32000H: October 8, 1962 - November 2, 1962 (Box 149)
  - 32001H - 34000H: November 2, 1962 - November 27, 1962 (Box 150)
  - 34001H - 36000H: November 27, 1962 - December 20, 1962 (Box 151)
  - 36001H - 38000H: December 20, 1962 - January 17, 1963 (Box 152)
  - 38001H - 40000H: January 17, 1963 - February 4, 1963 (Box 153)
  - 40001H - 42000H: February 4, 1963 - February 27, 1963 (Box 154)
  - 42001H - 44000H: February 27, 1963 - March 26, 1963 (Box 155)
  - 44001H - 46000H: March 26, 1963 - April 19, 1963 (Box 156)
  - 46001H - 48000H: April 22, 1963 - May 9, 1963 (Box 157)
  - 48001H - 50000H: May 9, 1963 - May 29, 1963 (Box 158)
  - 00001M - 02000M: May 28, 1963 - July 1, 1963 (Box 159)
  - 02001M - 04000M: July 1, 1963 - July 3, 1963 (Box 160)
  - 04001M - 06000M: July 8, 1963 - July 31, 1963 (Box 161)
  - 06001M - 08000M: July 31, 1963 - September 4, 1963 (Box 162)
  - 08001M - 10000M: September 4, 1963 - September 27, 1963 (Box 163)
  - 10001M - 12000M: September 27, 1963 - October 14, 1963 (Box 164)
  - 12001M - 14000M: October 14, 1963 - October 30, 1963 (Box 165)
  - 14001M - 16000M: October 30, 1963 - November 18, 1963 (Box 166)
  - 16001M - 18000M: November 19, 1963 - December 12, 1963 (Box 167)
  - 18001M - 20000M: December 12, 1963 - January 8, 1964. (Box 168)
  - 20001M - 22000M: January 8, 1964 - January 29, 1964. (Box 169)
  - 22001M - 24000M: January 29, 1964 - February 13, 1964 (Box 170)
  - 24001M - 26000M: February 13, 1964 - March 3, 1964 (Box 171)
  - 26001M - 28000M: March 3, 1964 - March 17, 1964 (Box 172)
  - 28001M - 30000M: March 17, 1964 - April 3, 1964 (Box 173)
  - 30001M - 32000M: April 3, 1964 - April 21, 1964 (Box 174)
  - 32001M - 34000M: April 21, 1964 - May 11, 1964 (Box 175)
  - 34001M - 36000M: May 11, 1964 – June 1, 1964 (Box 176)
  - 36001M - 38000M: June 1, 1964 - July 1, 1964 (Box 177)
  - 38001M - 40000M: July 1, 1964 - July 14, 1964 (Box 178)
  - 40001M - 42000M: July 14, 1964 - August 10, 1964 (Box 179)
  - 42001M - 44000M: August 10, 1964 – September 9, 1964 (Box 180)
  - 44001M - 46000M: September 4. 1964 - October 1, 1964 (Box 181)
  - 46001M - 48000M: October 1, 1964 - Oct 16, 1964 (Box 182)
  - 48001M - 50000M: October 16, 1964 - November 4, 1964 (Box 183)
  - 00001P - 02000P: November 4, 1964 - November 20, 1964 (Box 184)
  - 02001P - 04000P: November 20, 1964 - December 14, 1964 (Box 185)
  - 04001P - 06000P: December 14, 1964 - January 12, 1965 (Box 186)
  - 06001P - 08000P: January 12, 1965 - January 27, 1965 (Box 187)
  - 08001P - 10000P: January 27, 1965 - February 1, 1965 (Box 188)
  - 10001P - 12000P: February 1, 1965 - February 25, 1965 (Box 189)
  - 12001P - 14000P: February 24, 1965 - March 17, 1965 (Box 190)
  - 14001P - 16000P: March 17, 1965 - April 8, 1965 (Box 191)
  - 16001P - 18000P: April 8, 1965 - May 3, 1965 (Box 192)
  - 18001P - 20000P: May 3, 1965 - May 24, 1965 (Box 193)
  - 20001P - 22000P: May 24, 1965 - June 10, 1965 (Box 194)
  - 22001P - 24000P: June 10, 1965 - July 6, 1965 (Box 195)
  - 24001P - 26000P: July 6, 1965 - August 4, 1965 (Box 196)
  - 26001P - 28000P: August 4, 1965 - August 30, 1965 (Box 197)
  - 28001P - 30000P: August 30, 1965 - September 29, 1965 (Box 198)
  - 30001P - 32000P: September 27, 1965 - October 13, 1965 (Box 199)
  - 32001P - 34000P: October 13, 1965 - November 1, 1965 (Box 200)
  - 34001P - 36000P: November 1, 1965 - November 18, 1965 (Box 201)
  - 36001P - 38000P: November 18, 1965 - December 13, 1965 (Box 202)
  - 38001P - 40000P: December 13, 1965 - January 11, 1966 (Box 203)
  - 40001P - 42000P: January 11, 1966 - January 27, 1966 (Box 204)
  - 00001S - 02000S January 27, 1966 - February 10, 1966 (Box 205)
  - 02001S - 04000S February 10, 1966 - February 24, 1966 (Box 206)
  - 04001S - 06000S February 24, 1966 - March 10, 1966 (Box 207)
  - 06001S - 08000S March 10, 1966 - March 23, 1966 (Box 208)
  - 08001S - 10000S March 23, 1966 - April 11, 1966 (Box 209)
  - 10001S - 12000S April 11, 1966 - April 28, 1966 (Box 210)
  - 12001S - 14000S April 28, 1966 - May 17, 1966 (Box 211)
  - 14001S - 16000S May 17, 1966 - July 1, 1966 (Box 212)
  - 16001S - 18000S July 1, 1966 - July 1, 1966 (Box 213)
  - 18001S - 20000S July 1, 1966 - July 13, 1966 (Box 214)
  - 20001S - 22000S July 13, 1966 - August 1, 1966 (Box 215)
  - 22001S - 24000S August 1, 1966 - August 25, 1966 (Box 216)
  - 24001S - 26000S August 25, 1966 - September 21, 1966 (Box 217)
  - 26001S - 28000S September 21, 1966 - October 11, 1966 (Box 218)
  - 28001S - 30000S October 11, 1966 - October 27, 1966 (Box 219)
  - 30001S - 32000S October 27, 1966 - November 11, 1966 (Box 220)
  - 32001S - 34000S November 11, 1966 - December 5, 1966 (Box 221)
  - 34001S - 36000S December 5, 1966 - December 20, 1966 (Box 222)
  - 36001S - 38000S December 20, 1966 - January 13, 1967 (Box 223)
  - 38001S - 40000S January 12, 1967 - January 30, 1967 (Box 224)
  - 40001S - 42000S January 30, 1967 - February 14, 1967 (Box 225)
  - 42001S - 43700S February 14, 1967 - February 21, 1967 (Box 226)
  - 00001T - 02000T: February 27, 1967 - March 8, 1967 (Box 227)
  - 02001T - 04000T: March 8, 1967 - March 22, 1967 (Box 228)
  - 04001T - 06000T: March 22, 1967 - April 7, 1967 (Box 229)
  - 06001T - 08000T: April 7, 1967 - April 21, 1967 (Box 230)
  - 08001T - 10000T: April 21, 1967 - May 11, 1967 (Box 231)
  - 10001T - 12000T: May 11, 1967 - May 29, 1967 (Box 232)
  - 12001T - 14000T: May 29, 1967 - July 1, 1967 (Box 233)
  - 00001C - 02000C: July 1, 1967 - July 5, 1967 (Box 234)
  - 02001C - 04000C: July 5, 1967 - July 14, 1967 (Box 235)
  - 04001C - 06000C: July 14, 1967 – August 1, 1967 (Box 236)
  - 06001C - 08000C: August 1, 1967 - September1, 1967 (Box 237)
  - 08001C - 10000C: September 1, 1967 - September 27, 1967 (Box 238)
  - 10001C - 12000C: September 27, 1967 - October 12, 1967 (Box 239)
  - 12001C - 14000C: October 12, 1967 - October 27, 1967 (Box 240)
  - 14001C - 16000C: October 27, 1967 - November 14, 1967 (Box 241)
  - 16001C - 18000C: November 14, 1967 - November 30, 1967 (Box 242)
  - 18001C - 20000C: November 30, 1967 - December 13, 1967 (Box 243)
  - 20001C - 22000C: December 13, 1967 - January 8, 1968 (Box 244)
  - 22001C - 24000C: January 8, 1968 - January 24, 1968 (Box 245)
  - 24001C - 26000C: January 24, 1968 - February 7, 1968 (Box 246)
  - 26001C - 28000C: February 7, 1968 - February 21, 1968 (Box 247)
  - 28001C - 30000C: February 21, 1968 - March 6, 1968 (Box 248)
  - 30001C - 32000C: March 6, 1968 - March 21, 1968 (Box 249)
  - 32001C - 34000C: March 21, 1968 - March 21, 1968 (Box 250)
  - 34001C - 36000C: April 3, 1968 - April 16, 1968 (Box 251)
  - 36001C - 38000C: April 16, 1968 - May 13, 1968 (Box 252)
  - 38001C - 40000C: May 13, 1968 - May 24, 1968 (Box 253)
  - 40001C - 42000C: May 24, 1968 - June 10, 1968 (Box 254)
  - 42001C - 43168C: June 10, 1968 - June 14, 1968 (Box 255)
  - 43173C - 44000C: July 1, 1968 (Box 256)
  - 44001C - 46000C: July 1, 1968 - July 12, 1968 (Box 257)
  - 46001C - 48000C: July 12, 1968 - July 29, 1968 (Box 258)
  - 48001C - 50000C: July 29, 1968 - August 22, 1968 (Box 259)
  - 50001C - 52000C: August 22, 1968 - September 11, 1968 (Box 260)
  - 52001C - 54000C: September 12, 1968 - October 2, 1968 (Box 261)
  - 54001C - 56000C: October 2, 1968 - October 16, 1968 (Box 262)
  - 56001C - 58000C: October 16, 1968 - October 30, 1968 (Box 263)
  - 58001C - 60000C: October 30, 1968 - November 14, 1968 (Box 264)
  - 00001E - 02000E: November 14, 1968 - December 2, 1968 (Box 265)
  - 02001E - 04000E: December 2, 1968 - December 17, 1968 (Box 266)
  - 04001E - 06000E: December 17, 1968 - January 2, 1969 (Box 267)
  - 06001E - 08000E: January 2, 1969 - January 20, 1969 (Box 268)
  - 08001E - 10000E: January 20, 1969 - February 7, 1969 (Box 269)
  - 10001E - 12000E: February 7, 1969 - February 26, 1969 (Box 270)
  - 12001E - 14000E: February 26, 1969 - March 18, 1969 (Box 271)
  - 14001E - 16000E: March 18, 1969 - March 28, 1969 (Box 272)
  - 16001E - 18000E: March 28, 1969 - April 15, 1969 (Box 273)
  - 18001E - 20000E: April 15, 1969 - May 1, 1969 (Box 274)
  - 20001E - 22000E: May 1, 1969 - May 26, 1969 (Box 275)
  - 22001E - 24000E: May 26, 1969 - July 1, 1969 (Box 276)
  - 24001E - 26000E: July 1, 1969 - July 15, 1969 (Box 277)
  - 26001E - 28000E: July 15, 1969 - August 14, 1969 (Box 278)
  - 28001E - 30000E: August 14, 1969 - September 9, 1969 (Box 279)
  - 30001E - 32000E: July 1, 1969 - September 22, 1969 (Box 280)
  - 32001E - 34000E: September 22, 1969 - October 8, 1969 (Box 281)
  - 34001E - 36000E: October 9, 1969 - Oct 27, 1969 (Box 282)
  - 36001E - 38000E: October 27, 1969 - November 14, 1969 (Box 283)
  - 38001E - 40000E: November 14, 1969 - December 9, 1969 (Box 284)
  - 40001E - 42000E: December 9, 1969 - January 12, 1970 (Box 285)
  - 42001E - 44000E: January 12, 1970 - February 6, 1970 (Box 286)
  - 44001E - 46000E: February 6, 1970 - February 26, 1970 (Box 287)
  - 46001E - 48000E: February 26, 1970 - March 20, 1970 (Box 288)
  - 48001E - 50000E: March 20, 1970 - April 14, 1970 (Box 289)
  - 50001E - 52000E: April 13, 1970 - May 18, 1970 (Box 290)
  - 52001E - 54000E: May 18, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 291)
  - 54001E - 56000E: June 18, 1970 – August 31, 1970 (Box 292)
  - 56001E - 58000E: August 31, 1970 – November 10, 1970 (Box 293)
  - 00001F - 02000F: November 13, 1970 - February 25, 1971 (Box 294)
  - 02001F - 04000F: February 25, 1971 - July 28, 1971 (Box 295)
  - 04001F - 06000F: July 28, 1971 - December 10, 1971 (Box 296)
  - 06001F - 08000F: December 10, 1971 - April 25, 1972 (Box 297)
  - 08001F - 10000F: April 25, 1972 - March 14, 1972 (Box 298)
- Series IV: Accessions Records, 1961-1983
  - 101001 - 106324 January 23, 1961 - June 30, 1961 (Box 1)
  - 107001 - 112148 July 3, 1961 - December 27, 1961 (Box 2)
  - 201001 - 206296 January 2, 1962 - June 28, 1962 (Box 3)
  - 207001 - 210008 July 3, 1962 - October 1, 1962 (Box 4)
  - 210009 - 210136 (Box 5)
  - 2X1 - 2X1024 October 2, 1962 - December 26, 1962 (Box 5)
  - 3X0001 - 3X1990 January 1, 1963 - June 28, 1963 (Box 6)
  - 3X1991 - 3X3773 July 1, 1963 - December 31, 1963 (Box 7)
  - 4X0001 - 4X2147 January 1, 1964 - April 30, 1964 (Box 8)
  - 4X2148 - 4X4196 May 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 9)
  - 59501M - 59948P: June 19, 1964 - October 6, 1969 (Box 10)
  - 5X001 - 5X1000 Jan 7, 1965 - March 23, 1965 (Box 11)
  - 5X1001 - 5X2208 March 23, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 12)
  - 5X2209 - 5X3136 July 1, 1965 - September 30, 1965 (Box 13)
  - 5X3137 - 5X3971 October 1, 1965 - December 31, 1965 (Box 14)
  - 6X0001 - 6X0132 (Box 15)
  - 6X0173 - 6X1295 January 1, 1966 - March 31, 1966 (Box 15)
  - 6X1296 - 6X2573 April 1, 1966 - June 30, 1966 (Box 16)
  - 6X2574 - 6X3635 July 1, 1966 - September 30, 1966 (Box 17)
  - 6X3636 - 6X4563 October 31, 1966 - December 31, 1966 (Box 18)
  - 7X0001 - 7X1117 January 5, 1967 - April 14,1967 (Box 19)
  - 7X1118 - 7X2274 April 17, 1967 - June 22, 1967 (Box 20)
  - 7X2275 - 7X3394 June 23, 1967 - January 3, 1968 (Box 21)
  - 8X0001 - 8X1499 January 15, 1968 - August 2, 1968 (Box 22)
  - 8X1500 - 8X2799 August 2, 1968 - December 27, 1968 (Box 23)
  - 9X0001 - 9X1000 January 10, 1969 - June 25, 1969 (Box 24)
  - 9X1001 - 9X1632 July 7, 1969 - March 31, 1970 (Box 25)
  - 70X10001 - 70X1000 (Box 25)
  - 70X1001 - 70X2000 April 1, 1970 - July 14, 1970 (Box 26)
  - 70X2001 - 70X4000 July 14, 1970 - December 30, 1970 (Box 27)
  - 1X0001 - 1X1500 January 6, 1971 - June 9, 1971 (Box 28)
  - 1X1501 - 1X2572 June 9, 1971 - December 29, 1971 (Box 29)
  - 2X0001 - 2X2036 January 5, 1972 - December 20, 1972 (Box 30)
  - 3X0001 - 3X2248 January 5, 1973 - December 28, 1973 (Box 31)
  - 4X0001 - 4X1500 January 8, 1974 - July 19, 1974 (Box 32)
  - 4X1501 - 4X2976 July 19, 1974 - December 31, 1974 (Box 33)
  - 5X0001 - 5X1500 January 2, 1975 - October 31, 1975 (Box 34)
  - 5X1501 - 5X2840 November 3, 1975 - December 23, 1975 (Box 35)
  - 6X0001 - 6X1532 January 5, 1976 - June 15, 1976 (Box 36)
  - 6X1533 - 6X2936 June 15, 1976 - December 23, 1976 (Box 37)
  - 7X0001 - 7X0844 January 6, 1977 - May 31, 1977 (Box 38)
  - 7X0845 - 7X1972 June 1, 1977 - December 22, 1977 (Box 39)
  - 8X0001 - 8X1100 January 17, 1978 - June 13, 1978 (Box 40)
  - 8X1101 - 8X2201 June 13, 1978 - December 22, 1978 [serials acquisitions] (Box 41)
  - 9X0001 - 9X1020 January 9, 1979 - December 19, 1979 (Box 42)
  - 80X0001 - 80X0833 January 16, 1980 - December 31, 1980 (Box 43)
  - 1X0001 - 1X0712 January 12, 1981 - December 23, 1981 (Box 44)
  - 2X0001 - 2X0684 January 5, 1982 - December 23, 1982 (Box 45)
  - 3X0001 - 3X0360 January 15, 1983 - May 26, 1983 (Box 46)
- Series V: Permanent Order List: Encode I
  - 200000 - 201600 (Box 1)
  - 201601 - 204036 (Box 2)
  - 204037 - 206543 (Box 3)
  - 206544 - 208988 (Box 4)
  - 208989 - 211473 (Box 5)
  - 211474 - 213801 (Box 6)
  - 213802 - 216375 (Box 7)
  - 216376 - 219180 (Box 8)
  - 219181 - 222913 (Box 9)
  - 222914 - 226973 (Box 10)
  - 226974 - 231382 (Box 11)
  - 231383 - 235335 (Box 12)
  - 235336 - 238499 (Box 13)
  - 238500 - 242037 (Box 14)
  - 242038 - 245679 (Box 15)
  - 245680 - 249475 (Box 16)
  - 249476 - 253468 (Box 17)
  - 253469 - 256760 (Box 18)
  - 256761 - 260714 (Box 19)
  - 260715 - 263955 (Box 20)
  - 263956 - 266776 (Box 21)
  - 266777 - 270239 (Box 22)
  - 270240 - 272999 (Box 23.)
  - 273000 - 275587 (Box 24)
  - 275588 - 278615 (Box 25)
  - 278616 - 281462 (Box 26)
  - 281463 - 284499 (Box 27)
  - 284500 - 287829 (Box 28)
  - 287830 - 290988 (Box 29)
  - 290989 - 294028 (Box 30)
  - 294029 - 297887 (Box 31)
  - 297888 - 301096 (Box 32)
  - 301097 - 304675 (Box 33)
  - 304676 - 308977 (Box 34)
  - 308978 - 313360 (Box 35)
  - 313361 - 318209 (Box 36)
  - 318210 - 322438 (Box 37)
  - 322439 - 326885 (Box 38)
  - 326886 - 331079 (Box 39)
  - 331080 - 334999 (Box 40)
  - 335000 - 338800 (Box 41)
  - 338801 - 342661 (Box 42)